The End
Shoo!
Aaaaaah!
Iko!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
One bear successfully eliminated by our trap!
We know what you two really are and this is what you get!
From the beginning, we hated you.
But also we loved you from the beginning as well.
All we wanted was to become true friends with you.
So we had to cross the wall.
I had to have you all to myself.
Tomorrow's the day.
Oh, Sumika.
What was it you wanted to tell me?
Kirikuma!
Kirikuma Hiroshi!
This letter is hard. I barely even know what to say.
I guess I can start at the beginning. The moment I first met Kureha, I'll never forget that day.
Oh no! It's gone! I can't find it!
Grandma gave me that hairpin especially for today. I can't believe I lost it.
Are you looking for this?
Here.
It's yours, right?
Yes, thank you.
I know you probably don't remember that, but I do. And it meant the world to me.
I was so happy you were there. So happy to have met you.
And then, there was that storm. And I wanted to protect what you cared about.
You came out too!
We got soaked, remember? Sure, it was scary, but we ended up having such a good time.
I started feeling so close to you. Like it was just you and me. The only two people in the whole world.
It was heaven. I remember everything about that day.
But more importantly, I will always remember it, even when I'm old and gray.
The Moon Girl and the Forest Girl. Your mother wrote this?
Yep. It was actually her last book.
Since it was never published, it's the only copy. It's so good.
Mind if I read it?
Not at all.
Once upon a time, the worlds were divided into two parts by the sky.
There was the moon world and the forest world.
One day, a moon girl accidentally dropped her mother's precious pendant.
It fell far down into the forest.
A forest girl stumbled upon the pendant while she was out walking.
Surprised by its sparkling star, she found herself looking up at the sky to see where it came from.
She started to think what she could see might not be all there was and said,
There must be an amazing world beyond that sky.
Meanwhile, the moon girl couldn't stop wondering about the forest world and what happened to the pendant.
Where is mother's pendant, she said.
I have to go find it. There must be an amazing world beyond that sky.
Day after day, the moon girl and the forest girl looked at the sky, each one gazing from their own world.
At long last, they decided to appeal to Lady Kumaria, for she was the goddess of the sky.
The moon girl prayed,
Please help me, Lady Kumaria.
I want to go beyond the sky, so I can find my mother's lost pendant.
The forest girl prayed,
Please help me, Lady Kumaria.
I want to go beyond the sky, so I can deliver this lost star to the one who dropped it.
I am sorry, but you may not, said Kumaria, for the two worlds have been severed forever.
Wanting to cross that severance is pride, and pride, as you know, is a grave sin.
And yet they prayed again,
Please help us, we still want to go beyond the sky.
Reluctantly, Kumaria answered them,
There is one way to make your wish come true.
In the center of the sky is a place called the Door to Friendship.
If your love is true,
Your friend will be waiting for you.
You'll find her on the other side of that door.
When you see her, give her a promise kiss.
Do that, and your wish shall come true.
Kumaria asked the two girls a question,
Is your love the real thing?
Then she laid down a ladder for them,
Connecting the two worlds together once more.
They climbed the ladder until finally arriving at the center of the sky.
There they found a single, vast mirror standing like a wall in their path.
Each girl saw her own reflection in the mirror.
They heard Kumaria's voice say,
Now your friend is waiting just on the other side of that very door.
If you smash the you in the mirror to bits,
If you tear yourself apart,
She shall grant you a promised kiss.
But beware,
This may cost you your life.
I will ask you one more time,
Is your love the real thing?
The girls stared at themselves in the mirror for a very long time.
Is that the end?
No, the story doesn't have an ending.
A bear killed mom.
She never got the chance to finish it.
How sad.
So, what would you do if it was about you?
Uh...
You know, that part in the story.
Would you risk your life in order to break the mirror?
I'm not really sure.
Let me think.
I would break it.
What?
I'd shoot my reflection.
I'd shoot.
Because I would do anything to prove my love was true.
In that moment,
I decided I wouldn't back down on love either.
No matter what happened.
I would do anything to prove my love too.
Now, ladies, it's time to decide on the next evil to exclude.
Let's search evil!
Oh, ladies, I have bad news.
It seems we have a traitor among our ranks.
Kurehatsu Baki was the one set up to be the next evil.
Unfortunately, before we can target her,
we must first exclude the traitor.
I'm sure she agrees.
Right, Sumika Izumino?
Kureha, I'm sorry.
I jumped into the storm myself,
and I did it willingly.
At the time,
I thought if I could prove my love,
I wouldn't mind getting hurt,
even heartbroken.
But then,
I realized I was wrong.
It wouldn't be me the Invisible Storm would break.
It would wind up being you,
the one I care about most.
Good.
You wrote the letter.
Oh, Kauru.
Thanks.
Great work.
I can take it now.
That way, I'll be ready to give it to Kureha.
What's the problem?
About the letter,
would you mind holding off a bit?
I'd like to wait until we celebrate Kureha's birthday here,
at the garden.
Is that okay?
Fine, whatever.
Just don't forget,
I have to be Kureha's new friend.
That's the only way we can make sure the storm will pass her by.
Yeah.
I can't stop the storm,
but I can protect Kureha,
as long as I'm her new friend.
I know it puts you in a terrible position,
but we have no other choice if we want to save her.
I still think I should do it.
Deliver the letter, I mean.
No.
Let me.
This is the last love I ever get to give her,
so it has to be done right.
It has to be me.
Okay.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
See ya.
Kureha.
This will be my present to you,
because I understand now.
I promise to never back down on love.
I owe you one.
Thank you for saving my life.
You told me the truth about Ginko and Lulu,
that they were bears disguised as humans.
Because of you,
I got to set a trap in advance.
Although...
We know what you are,
and this is what you get!
Bear Flash!
I can't believe that stupid bear,
who knew she'd have a trick up her sleeve.
But it's not a problem.
The plane is still going off without a hitch.
Yes, Sumika's death was definitely unexpected,
but your idea of using it was inspired.
Pure genius.
Tomorrow, it'll finally be Kureha Tsubaki's birthday,
and I think we'll really enjoy it.
Oh, no.
Don't tell me.
Leave me alone, for your own sake!
I wonder where they could have gone.
I was planning to apologize, too.
Growl!
Ginko!
Oh, hang in there!
Growl, sniffle!
Dang it!
Stupid Kaoru, Harishima!
It doesn't make any sense!
How did she even know we were bears?
Reya,
I can't help but be reminded of the day I swore my love to you.
And now, it's your daughter's turn.
I wonder what she'll get from her friend on her birthday.
So that it's perfect, since it's my present to you.
Sumika,
I promise to accept your gift,
and I'll do what you asked me to.
Hmm.
Hey, Kureha,
do you remember the day of the entrance ceremony?
What?
Pummeled by the cold wind that scattered the cherry blossoms.
A girl searched for something, but she couldn't seem to find it.
I felt bad for Sumika.
No one helped her look for it at all.
Although, why would they?
It was just some cheap hairpin, nothing to get upset about.
But you, you're not like the rest of us.
Tell me something.
Why haven't you lost hope yet?
The world is cruel.
You've lost things,
had them taken from you.
Why don't you become invisible?
Well,
I think it's because I don't forget love.
I don't understand what that means.
It means,
as long as you don't forget love,
you'll never, ever be alone.
And if you don't give up on love,
even if you lose something,
you won't be invisible.
What's that?
It's a letter from Sumika.
She gave it to me not too long ago.
This,
this is my birthday present.
I'm supposed to read it at the flower bed.
So, Kureha,
it means a lot that you're giving us a chance
to make amends for all this.
Thank you.
I'm super excited about your birthday party, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Thank you.
Oh, there's no need to thank me, silly.
Especially considering your love
is about to be utterly destroyed
by the invisible storm.
Kureha!
Ginko, you're alive!
Oh, Lulu's so happy, Ginko!
What a relief!
That was terrifying!
Lulu was so worried!
She didn't know what she'd do if you died!
Lulu did everything she could think of!
She carried you all the way to here
and stayed up the whole night
taking care of you!
Oh, no!
Today is Kureha's birthday!
Growl, growl, growl!
Huh?
I said today is Kureha's birthday!
Hello?
Is your love the real thing?
This is a challenge from the Wall of Severance.
Ginko, Yurishiro,
if your love is true,
you need to get to the flower bed.
The moon girl is there right now
awaiting your arrival.
Do I know a moon girl?
All you have to do is give yourself over to the flames.
Only then will your love be approved.
Kureha!
Are you trying to tell me
the moon girl is supposed to be Kureha?
All right.
I wonder if the promised kiss
will come to pass now.
We shall see.
For that is sexy.
Shabba da do.
On your birthday, Kureha.
We wish you well.
Happy birthday!
Thank you, guys.
Don't forget your promise.
You told Sumika you'd read her letter right here.
Yeah.
Kureha,
the girl standing in front of you
is...
is your new friend.
What does this mean?
Exactly what it says.
It's pretty obvious when you think about it.
That's Sumika's breakup letter to you.
Seems she's trying to give you a gift, too.
Her final present for you
was to make sure you had a new friend.
One that wasn't her.
But we have no intention
of making friends with you,
Kureha Tsubaki.
I can't imagine it feels very good
to realize you were both tricked.
We were tricked?
That's right.
Surprise.
I was the one who had Sumika
write the letter to you
in the first place.
Her death screwed up
the original plan.
Yet fortunately,
we got to use that letter
to punish the real evil anyway.
The girl who refuses
to follow social cues.
In order to wish you
the happiest of birthdays,
Kureha Tsubaki,
this is a little something special
from us to you.
Happy birthday!
The time has come
for us to exclude the evil.
Exclude!
Tell me,
does evil get to have
any friends?
No friends!
Tell me,
does evil get crushed,
crushed by the invisible storm
as punishment?
Crush as punishment!
She's excluded!
Good job, ladies!
Kureha Tsubaki
just snapped like a twig!
Yay!
You did it!
Tragic.
You won't get
any new friends.
On top of that,
you'll never be able
to accept
Sumika Izunino's
final gift.
Oh, what a pity.
At least now you know
the emotion of love
is powerless and pointless.
No use for this anymore!
No, Sumika wrote that!
It's such a beautiful smile.
I want you to always
smile like that,
like a flower.
That's my love.
It's funny.
Even if I had to watch you
from a distance,
I would be happy
just to see that smile.
Please, it's Sumika's love!
She gave it to me!
Rell!
Oh, Kura!
What, Kinko?
Okay, everyone.
Looks like the party's over.
Let's get out of here!
Let's go!
We're on!
We're waiting!
Ah!
He won't!
He'll never back down on love!
Kinko!
Ginko, you dummy!
Lulu would have killed you
if you'd really died this time!
What were you thinking?
Why would you do that,
Ginko?
You're a dummy too!
She did it because she loves you!
She...
She loves me?
That's right!
Ginko loves you so much!
Look at what she's done!
For you!
Don't waste her love!
Please, don't waste it!
Kurea, the girl standing in front of you
is your new friend.
Is this for real?
She's my new friend?
I think I got here a little early.
Still, I'm gonna have to fix this place fast.
The flower bed has to be packed full of flowers again before Kureha's birthday.
Well, good morning, Sumika.
Such a lovely morning.
And I'm practically starving.
Mitsuko, is that you?
That day, I committed a serious crime.
I am a criminal bear.